

## Khandaker Zoad Pial

KhandakerZoadPial Control KhandakerZoadPial

Bangladesh
 Python-Django Developer
 years of experience
 khpial27@gmail.com

As a computer science graduate, I love diving into technology and programming. I'm all about learning, often choosing long tutorial videos over movies to improve my skills. I specialize in Django and web development, where I create sleek and functional solutions. I enjoy tackling new challenges and pushing the limits of what's possible in tech. With my curiosity and innovative mindset, I turn ideas into reality through code.

Skills: Python Django HTML CSS Bootstrap Ajax BeautifulSoup Version Control Deployment Excel

Capsule Network Pandas Open CV

### Experience

Fiverr Aug 2021 to Present

Freelance Django Developer

Have been working as a freelance Django developer on fiverr.com and completed more than 50 individual projects

Coderstrust Bangladesh coderstrustbd.com

Dec 2023 to Mar 2024

Mentor Barishal

Was responsible for conducting classes under Sheikh Kamal IT and Incubation center project.

P UGV Aug 2022 to Nov 2022

**Backend Developer** 

We were responsible for building the student management system, finance, and employee management system. This was the rebuilding project of my university's entire system. I was a core member of the development team.

TheAdviceOnline Sep 2021 to Jul 2022

Fullstack Developer

- Worked on the back-end part of the application along with the front-end
- Managed the version control with GitHub
- Was responsible for the deployment staging and production server.

#### Education

University of Global Village, UGV ugv.edu.bd

Jan 2019 to Jan 2023

B.Sc, Computer Science & Engineering

3.60 out of 4

# **Projects**

#### **TheAdviceOnline**

Al powered question answer website.

Python, Github, Pythonanywhere, Django, Bootstrap, Facebook/Google Authentication, CloudinaryCDN

Python, Github, Ajax, Bootstrap, Google Cloud Platform, Django
Social
Certificates
ACM ICPC Dhaka Reginal 2021 onsite ACM 2021
Publications ————————————————————————————————————
A Comparative Analysis for Bengali Handwritten Character & Digit Recognition using Capsule Network IEEE Explore Dec 2023
Languages ————————————————————————————————————
English Fluent Bengali Native

**Eternity Album**